You may notice, that if the amount we invest in each stock of
你可能注意到了 如果为投资组合中的每支股票
our portfolio is tied to the Alpha value that we get from daily data,
分配的金额与通过每日数据获得的 Alpha 值对应
then we would be constantly buying and selling
那么我们每天都需要买入和卖出
every day in order to follow the signal faithfully.
才能严格遵守 Alpha 信号
In other words, as the Alpha vector changes every day,
也就是说 因为 Alpha 向量每天都变化
we'd have to adjust our portfolio weights every day also.
所以我们也需要每天调整投资组合权重
We also have to address what happens to our Alpha vector when we encounter outliers,
我们还需要考虑当数据集中有离群值或极端值时
or extreme values in the data.
Alpha 向量会怎样
If we have had a large increase in the office signal for one stock,
如果某支股票的 Alpha 信号增大很多
then a sharp decrease the next day,
而第二天下降很多
this would effectively tell us to buy a lot of
那么这个信号告诉我们买入很多该股票
that stock and then sell a lot of that stock the next day.
第二天再卖出很多该股票
This may or may not be warranted.
这种做法不一定合适
In the real world, trading costs money.
在现实中 交易有成本
So, we want to be very confident that if we go to make a trade and bear that cost,
如果我们做出交易并承担这种成本
that it is indeed warranted.
必须完全有信心利润可以抵消成本
Some ways to keep extreme values from leading to unnecessarily large trades,
有一些方法可以避免极端值造成不必要的大量交易
are by clipping very large and small values at for
包括去除很大和很小的值
example the 95th percentile and the fifth percentile.
例如以第 95 百分位和第 5 百分位为分界线
This process is called winsorizing.
这个流程称为缩尾处理
Here's an example of winsorizing in
举个例子
Alpha vector which has Alpha values for each stock, for a single day.
这些是每支股票一天的 Alpha 值
For any number that exceeds the 95th percentile,
对于任何第 95 百分位以上的数字
we've replaced that outlier with a number at the 95th percentile.
我们将这些数字替换为第 95 百分位的数字
Also for any values that are below the fifth percentile,
并且对于任何第 5 百分位以下的数字
we replace those with a number at the fifth percentile.
我们将这些数字替换为第 5 百分位的数字
Again, this is called winsorizing.
这个就是缩尾技巧
We can also deal with outliers,
还有一种处理离群值的技巧
by setting a maximum magnitude allowed waits for any single stock.
即对任何一支股票的权重大小都设定上限
Note that we would handle outliers for each Alpha vector which may be updated each day.
注意 我们需要处理每个 Alpha 向量的离群值 这些向量可能会每天更新
Even when we've dealt with outliers,
即使处理了离群值
there's still the issue of whether it makes sense to buy and sell
但是依然需要考虑
based on the signal if their relative magnitudes for the Alpha values don't change.
如果 Alpha 值的相对大小没有变化 是否有必要根据 Alpha 信号买卖股票
Let's again take the example of Apple and Alphabet.
再以 Apple 和 Alphabet 为例
One day, Apple's Alpha value is 0.33 and Alphabet's value is 0.31.
某一天 Apple 的 Alpha 值为 0.33 Alphabet 的 Alpha 值为 0.31
What if on the next day,
第二天
Apple's Alpha value increased by 0.01 and Alphabet's Alpha value also increased by 0.01.
Apple 的 Alpha 值增加了 0.01 Alphabet 的 Alpha 值也增加了 0.01
If we translated these directly into portfolio weights,
如果我们直接将这些变化体现到投资组合权重上
the weights would change slightly from day one today two.
第二天的权重与第一天相比变化很小
But the important thing to notice is that we'd still be
需要注意的是
putting more money on Apple relative to Alphabet.
分配给 Apple 的金额依然比 Alphabet 的高
So, maybe we wouldn't actually want to change our positions at all.
所以也许根本不用改变头寸
Often what we want to do,
通常我们希望
is have a more robust version of the signal which is able to withstand outliers,
创建更稳健的信号 它能够消除离群值
handle noise in the data,
处理数据噪点
and also keep us from making potentially excessive traits.
并且避免做出过多的交易
We can handle this with a ranking.
我们可以通过排名来实现